A Guide to the Papers of Ann Beattie
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Ann Beattie 1986-1998
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
10414-aa
This collection consists of ca. 65 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Stored off-site. Users must request boxes 48 hours in advance of desired use. Neither drop-in nor next-day requests can be fulfilled. For additional information, contact Special Collections.
Access restrictions apply to specific student and staff records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.). Other records may also be restricted.
Acquisition Information
These papers were loaned to the University of Virginia by Ann Beattie on July 22, 1998.
Scope and Content Information
This addition to the papers of American novelist and short story writer, Ann Beattie, consists of ca. 65 items (.5 cubic box), ca. 1986-1988, including typescripts and printed versions of short stories, essays, articles, and a novel, Phantom Pain; dust jackets; promotional materials and book catalogs featuring the books of Ann Beattie; interviews with Ann Beattie; reviews of her books; a small amount of correspondence; student evaluations; and printed material on literary conferences, retreats, ceremonies and awards.
Contents List
- "Boot Top Blue" n.d.
- Brief Articles, Essays, and Short Stories 1991-1998, n.d.
- Correspondence 1993-1998, n.d.
- "Cosmos" n.d.
- Dust Jackets & Promotional Material 1995
- "The Famous Poet, Amid Bougainvillea" n.d.
- "The Four Night Fight" n.d.
- Interviews 1993-1997
- Literary Conferences, Schools, Ceremonies, Retreats, etc. 1992-1997
- Phantom Pain n.d., 2 folders
- Preservation Article on Key West 1996
- Reviews 1997-1998
- "See the Pyramids" n.d.
- "Skeletons" 1986
- "Solitude" n.d.
- Student Evaluations n.d.
- Printed Work by Ann Beattie in Literary Journals, including "Buried Treasure," "Fireback," "See the Pyramids," and "Park City" 1994-1997